[{"answer": "You've got that (INAUDIBLE) clause.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Howard Stern, how much of his private parts did he show?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "-- I remember being dragged into this sort of side dungeon and one of your producers saying, OK, this is how this works.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "I love Larry King.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Do you like Larry?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Listen, I like you.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "I want to have a third show, all right?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "It was also true.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Who's going to buy into that?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "No, I am the king of all media.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "But you've never denied being the king of all media?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Does that make you the king?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I want to play you a clip.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Who's going to care?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "When is he starting?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, you -- it's not on.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "No one's watching that thing anyway?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "No, I want you to be successful.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "But you don't apologize?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I think you have to have a sense of yourself.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What is the secret of being a long-time, successful entertainer in America, do you think?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "If you've got the money that you made, the success you've enjoyed, the status and everything that comes with it, what would motivate you to get out of bed at 3:30, 4:00 every day to carry on doing this?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "I think -- my parents listen every day.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Do they listen to the show?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Rarely.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "And how often does he say to you, \"Great show, Howard\"?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I think it's my identity.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Once your dad's called you a genius, you've had all the success and the money, I'm curios as to what makes you, Howard Stern, at 4:00 in the morning, when everyone else is asleep, say, getting out of bed and I'm going to back into battle on the show that often drives me crazy, I'm not even sure I enjoy it?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "TERN: Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Insecurity?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I'm fascinated by sex.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Are you -- are you sex mad?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "TERN: I said -- well, I said, they're beautiful.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What did you say to them when you examined them?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "It's nothing.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Then what happens?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "They were there with their boyfriends.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "They seemed to be proud to show --", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How did the boyfriends feel?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "The answer was no for me.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "You said yes or no?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "You never cheated?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I've been faithful.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "You're always being faithful?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "ORGAN: It's a kind of contradiction.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Why are you shocked by that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Would you say physically impaired?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "You want to really get into this?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I'm not getting into that.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How many inches are you?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I'm interviewing you.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Have you ever measured?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Have you ever taken Viagra?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "No, I don't need it.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Never tried it?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, I've had a history with drugs.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Have you ever taken any drug?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "But for myself, I do not -", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Even though you went through that kind of experience?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "As a father, do you actually believe in legalizing drugs as a father?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I think that if my -- I think my kids are very strong, they have their heads together.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Would you like your kids to have access free to illegal drugs?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, Beth is my best friend.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What are you thoughts when you look at that picture?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "My wife's not here, luckily.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Where is your wife?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Are you never about three months down the road?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "This interview is doing pretty well.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "About what?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, listen, you know, I've never released financial deals although I read in the paper every day how much I'm worth every day.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "How much was your new five-year deal with?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No, I never took a pay cut.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "You didn't?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I'm doing -- I'm going to be doing less hours.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "More or less?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I would say it's about the same.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "More or less than the last deal, as a salary?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "A little more for a little less work?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "A better deal.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "It was a better deal for you?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Well, listen, yes, I do have stock.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "When you announced the deal, the stock price went up by 20 percent, presuming you have stock?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Let me show you the first deal, because we can talk about that now.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "But who knows?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "They were -- they were driving me insane.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "So, they were restricting you too much with the fines?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "You don't dispute being worth hundreds of millions -- maybe even a billion -- you worth a billion?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Oprah is worth way more money than I am.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you worth a quarter of an Oprah?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Does that annoy you?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I mean, Oprah -- Oprah was in syndication.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "That the queen of all media is worth more than you?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "And as far -- he did a terrible thing to Conan O'Brien.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "What did you think of what he did to Conan O'Brien?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "I mean, wasn't it just business, really?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "It -- it's such a -- you ever read Bill Carter's book on it?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "But he had made certain guarantees to Conan.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "-- and someone else comes along?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Well, how is it that you're number one in -- in what you do?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Well, Letterman being one of them.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Who do you most admire in your business?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Probably the moment this show finishes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "When is this show going off the air?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "The hair is real, and I -- and I --", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Is it real -- that hair?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "I do not color it.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "And you dye it, obviously?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "-- I have some gray in it.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I am virile.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Do you feel -- does it make you feel virile?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Are you -- are you romantic?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I -- that's a tough one.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Just ask Howard, is he good in bed?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Well, you know, listen.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "How many have said no?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "With happiness, or with despair?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "Well no.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "I don't know, you watch porno?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "My real view is this, that it -- it's a sad day when I -- I interview many porno stars and I'm fascinated by their lives, because I say, you know, the -- the parents must be like out of their minds.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "What's your real view?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "First of all, David is a friend of mine.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "Or do you feel uneasy?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "I wrote him an e-mail immediately.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "So as his friend, though, when it backfires, did you feel uneasy about it?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "Well, a joke -- I started to believe it.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 885, "question": "You meant it as a bit of a joke, right?", "qSentId": 884}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "Are you -- are you tempted to go again?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "I think America is the greatest country in the world.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 940, "question": "What do you think it's come to?", "qSentId": 939}, {"answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1010, "question": "TERN: He left for a personal reason?", "qSentId": 1009}, {"answer": "Bigger than yours.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1015, "question": "How big is your penis?", "qSentId": 1014}, {"answer": "I love watching these -- like Miley Cyrus grow up and then start taking all her clothes off.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1023, "question": "And when you see Miley Cyrus, Justin Bieber dominate, what do you think?", "qSentId": 1022}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1047, "question": "An age thing?", "qSentId": 1046}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1050, "question": "Do you worry about getting old?", "qSentId": 1049}, {"answer": "TERN: I don't know.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1056, "question": "Could you imagine being 80 and happy?", "qSentId": 1055}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1063, "question": "Well what's been -- what's been the moment in your life which, if you had five minutes to live, you would have again?", "qSentId": 1062}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1085, "question": "Did he ever tell you that he loves you?", "qSentId": 1084}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110118pmt", "aSentId": 1103, "question": "In the end, you are just a shameless little plugger, aren't you?", "qSentId": 1102}]